The tax bureau seized that money
So you still have to pay it back
That's not my problem either
Then
Go get it from Zoe then
Go find Zoe
She's in prison
You want me to go in there after her
Are you wishing prison on me
The deal was she'd pay my debt
In exchange for the formula
Cut the crap
You signed the papers
Looking at you, you clearly have no money
These kidneys should fetch some cash
Take him away
Don't take my kidneys! Let me go
Let my son go
Don't harvest my kidneys
Let me go! Don't take my kidneys
Let go of my son
Mom, help me
Leave Daniel alone
My son-in-law is rich
I'll make him pay the debt
Everyone knows your son-in-law
He cut ties with your family long ago
Like he'd pay for you
If he doesn't pay up
I'll drink poison and die at his door
I'll give you one last chance
I want the money by 6 PM tonight